AZAR BARFIPOUR

SUMMARY

Former software supporter and developer with a background in software engineering and 4+ years of experience looking for opportunities in front-end development. I have worked for large companies and have had the opportunity to work alongside excellent and impactful software teams. Currently, working on front-end development, I am very eager to join an organization where I can have a great impact.

SKILLS

WEB: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Express, Mongoose, Node.JS, TypeScript
FRAMEWORKS, LIBRARIES AND ENVIRONMENTS: React.js, Angular, jQuery, SASS, Bootstrap
SYSTEMS, CMS AND DATABASES: Git, GitHub, Bitbucket, Firebase, PostgreSQL, SQLserver, MongoDB

PROJECTS

Meetup App Feb. 2022

A book event application for searching and booking events Technical specifications: React, HTML, CSS, Firebase

E-Commerce App Apr. 2022

An e-commerce React app for handicraft products, using Redux and Google authentication. Users can add to cards and remove from it. Technical specifications: React, Redux, HTML, CSS, Google authentication, Firebase

Weather-Location App May. 2022

A React app using API for checking weather by location. Users can see the weather by allowing access to their location. Moreover, users can check any place on the map.

Technical specifications: React, HTML, CSS, Google map API and Open Weather API

EMPLOYMENT

Front End Developer | Freelivenet, Vancouver

May. 2022 - Present

- Testing, debugging and developing an Angular API Portal using Git and Bitbucket
- Working on UI/UX enhancements
- Working on creating embed code

Data Entry | Terry Beech MP's Office, Burnaby

Jul. 2021

Analyzed people surveys emails and entered into the application

Software Support Specialist | Behban software Co, Tehran

Sep. 2015 - Oct. 2020

- . Created more than 100 reports for big companies such as the biggest oil company in the Middle East from their huge data using SQL
- Debugged, solved and developed more than 50 customer's demands each day and traveled around the country to install the app
- . Created forms in ASP classic by using ASP, HTML, CSS and JavaScript, collaborating with multiple teams and seniors at the company

EDUCATION

Web Development Diploma | CICCC, Vancouver, Canada

Aug. 2021 - Present

HTML, CSS, JanaScript, React.js, Node.js, SQL, Python, etc.

UAP | University Canada West, Vancouver, Canada

Apr. 2021

Academic English course

Computer Software Engineering B.S. | UOK, Sanandaj, IRAN

Feb. 2015

Thesis: Web site design by Joomla Advisor: Fardin Akhlaghian